digibank24.com 2012-10-05

# Privacy statement - DigiBank24

We take protection of your private information very seriously. In what follows, we inform you in detail about how we treat your data.

## Use of your personal information

You can visit our website without having to provide any personal information. We only collect personal information from you if you provide it voluntarily in connection with ordering a product, opening of a customer account or signing up for one of our newsletters. We do not link your personal information with the statistical analysis of visitor activity we perform with installed statistics software, which records the host IP address, the date and time of access, the browser type, browser settings, operating system, screen resolution, browsed pages and site of origin. This data is used exclusively for optimizing our website by analyzing and comparing general information about user behavior that is unrelated to individual persons. We automatically collect IP addresses and information pertaining to use of our website as soon as you avail yourself of one of our online services. The information collected in this manner aids us in analyzing visitor traffic and navigation on our website, including, but not limited to, the number and frequency of visitors and subscribers to the website and the length of visits. We use the collected information to send you email notifications of new or existing DigiBank24 products and services, of our special offers or to otherwise contact you in order to improve existing functionality or to develop new functionality, products or services and to make it possible for you to personalize contents and advertisements that you view based on personal preferences or settings.

## Order information

We use information that you provide in connection with an order only to fill and process your order. Insofar as it is necessary for supplying the goods, we will pass your information on to the respective product manufacturer, licensor or service provider or the shipping company that will deliver your order (name, address, possibly a phone number to set a delivery date.) If necessary, we will give your payment information to the banking institution we use for payments processing. We do not share your information with any other third parties. Your personal information will be erased after expiry of data retention periods provided for in tax and commercial statutes.

## Newsletter

When your sign up for our newsletter, we use your name and email address with your consent strictly for our own promotional purposes, until you unsubscribe from the newsletter. You may cancel your subscription at any time by sending us a brief note or by deactivating receipt of the newsletter in your user profile.

## Cookies

When you sign up with us or want to place an order, we require your customer information. For this purpose, we store information about the contents of your shopping cart in so-called “cookies,” which can be called up again the next time you visit us. Cookies are small text files that are stored on your computer. Having data deposited in cookies frees you from needing to fill our forms out again. We use two types of cookies: so-called session cookies, which are deleted from your hard disk when your terminate the browser session and the type that remains on your computer after you end the session, which allows us to recognize your computer the next time you visit (permanent cookies.) These permanent cookies have a six-month life. Your browser will let you delete all cookies at any time; moreover, it will let you manage how you accept cookies from this site and to block them if you choose to.

## Inquiries

You have the right to receive information about your stored data as well as the right if necessary to have this data corrected, blocked or deleted free of charge. For questions concerning collection, processing or use of your personal data, or for inquiries, correction, blocking or deletion of data as well as rescinding of consents given, please contact Christian Neise at (+49) (231) 2206834, support@digibank24.com

## Information security

We protect our website and other systems by employing technical and organizational measures against loss, destruction, access, modification or dissemination of your data by unauthorized persons. Access to your customer account (if you have one) is only possible with your personal password. Always guard your sign-on information and close your browser window after you complete your communication with us, especially if you share your computer with others. We encrypt sensitive data (credit card numbers or email addresses) with SSL. Our security measures conform with generally accepted industry standards, so that personal information shared with us is protected as much as possible during transmission as well as after we receive it (for example, with redundant cables, UPS, alarm systems, cooling, email virus filters, email spam filters, backup, etc.) In spite of this, no internet transmission and no storage method can be one hundred percent secure.

## Blogs and reviews

If you use a bulletin board, blog or open forum, all information you post there can be read, collected or utilized by other users. We are not responsible for personal information that you make available on these platforms. Our websites contain reviews that may contain personal information. Persons who publish their reviews consent to having this information published.

## Links

When you click on the link of a third party business, you leave our website and are taken to the selected website. Since we have no control over the activities of these third party businesses, we cannot take any responsibility for whatever these third party businesses might do with the personal information.
